Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America Records WAG.235
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Files of Michael J. Quill, 1928-1970.
  - Subseries I:A: TWU Presidential Files, 1928-1970
    - Quill, Michael J.: Memorials, 1966-1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Quill, Michael J.: Correspondence, 1937-1944 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Quill, Michael J.: Roaring Brook Lake Property (Putnam County), 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Quill Scholarship Fund, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Quill Testimonial Dance, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Radio Speeches, 1938-1949 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Radio Speeches, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Railroad Division, Undated; 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Rates of Pay: Telephone Workers and Utility Workers, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Reports, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Reuther, Walter, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Rice, Father Charles O., 1939 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Right Wing; Anti-Labor, Anti-Communist Material, Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Roosevelt, Anna (Halsted), 1965 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: Death of, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, Jr., 1950 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Rosenberg Case, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Royal Visit (King George VI and Queen Elizabeth) to NYC, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Ryan, Frank, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Ryan, Jack (International Representative), 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Sacher, Harry, 1936-1941 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco, CA: Muni Carmen, Undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Santo Defense Committee, 1941; 1942 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Santo Defense Fund, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Santo Defense Fund: Medical Staff Contributions, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Santo Farewell Party (U.S. Army), 1942 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Santo, John, 1936-1947 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Santo, John: Clippings, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Santo, John: Deportation, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Santo, John: Military service, 1942-1944 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Siegel, Aaron: Selective Service Status, 1944-1945 (Box 20a, Folder 1)
    - Singer Sewing Machine Co.: Strike (Elizabeth NJ), 1949 (Box 20a, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Randall (Pete), Undated (Box 20a, Folder 3)
    - Solidarity Fund, 1957 (Box 20a, Folder 4)
    - Song: "Thank God for the CIO" (Palahak-Kivlan), 1941 (Box 20a, Folder 5)
    - Southern Negro Congress (A. Herndon), 1938 (Box 20a, Folder 6)
    - Spain, 1947 (Box 20a, Folder 7)
    - Spanish Civil War, 1937-1940 (Box 20a, Folder 8)
    - Special Cases, 1960 (Box 20a, Folder 9)
    - Speeches, Undated; 1938-1940; 1943; 1952 (Box 20a, Folder 10)
    - Sports (TWU), 1941 (Box 20a, Folder 11)
    - Staff: TWU, 1955-1957 (Box 20a, Folder 12)
    - State County and Municipal Workers of America, 1937-1940; 1946 (Box 20a, Folder 13)
    - Stevenson, Adlai, 1965 (Box 20a, Folder 14)
    - Taft-Hartley Act, Undated; 1947; 1954-1959 (Box 20a, Folder 15)
    - Taft-Hartley Act: Repeal, 1948-1949 (Box 20a, Folder 16)
    - Taft-Hartley Law: Compliance, 1948 (Box 20a, Folder 17)
    - Taxi Drivers Organizing Campaign, 1934-1944 (Box 20a, Folder 18)
    - Taxi Drivers Organizing Campaign, 1947-1949; 1961-1965 (Box 20a, Folder 19)
    - Taxi Organizing, Salt Lake City, UT, 1948 (Box 20a, Folder 20)
    - Teachers Unions, 1960-1966 (Box 20a, Folder 21)
    - Teachers Unions: Clippings, 1960-1966 (Box 20a, Folder 22)
    - Teachers Union: Local 555, 1945 (Box 20a, Folder 23)
    - Thomas, Norman, 1965 (Box 20a, Folder 24)
    - Traffic: NYC Department of Traffic, Annual Report, 1956 (Box 20a, Folder 25)
    - Traffic, New York University Conference, 1956 (Box 20a, Folder 26)
    - Transit Cuts (NYC): Rally and Campaign to Protest, 1954 (Box 20a, Folder 27)
    - Transit Labor Data: Research Material, 1941 (Box 20a, Folder 28)
    - Transportation Employees Industrial Union, 1941 (Box 20a, Folder 29)
    - Transport Voice: Advertising, 1951 (Box 20a, Folder 30)
    - Twentieth Anniversary, 1953-1954 (Box 20a, Folder 31)
    - TWU Express, 1949-1953; 1955-1957 (Box 20a, Folder 32)
    - United China Relief, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - United Committee for Collective Bargaining, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - United Federal Workers of America, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - United Mine Workers of America (UMWA): Committee for Autonomy and Self-Government, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - United Mineworkers (John L. Lewis): Dispute, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, 1937-1939 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - United States Office of Defense Transportation, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - United States Senate Finance Committee (Quill testimony), 1943 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - United Steelworkers of America, 1949-1952 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - United Steelworkers of America (California), 1947 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - United Telephone Organizers (vs. CWA): William A. Olsen and William Genoese, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - United Transport Service Employees, CIO, 1953-1955 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Utility Workers Organizing Committee, 1941-1944 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Victory Rally, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Vietnam War, Quill on, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Voluntary Relief Department, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Wage Rates (bus), 1945 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Wages: Transit Employees (New York City), 1952 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Wagner, Robert F.: Clippings, 1953-1955 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Wagner, Robert F.: Mayoral Campaign, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Wagner, Robert F.: Mayoral Campaign, Clippings, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Wagner, Robert F.: Mayoral Campaign (New York City CIO Council Support for), 1953 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Wagner, Robert F.: Mayoral Campaign (TWU Support for), 1953 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Wallace, Henry A.: Presidential Campaign, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Wallace, Henry A.: Presidential Campaign, Clippings, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Wallace, Henry A.: Presidential Campaign, Pamphlets and Leaflets, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - War Bond Drives/Victory Loans, 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - War Loan, Undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Welfare Workers Strike, 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - WEVD: "The March of Labor", Undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Wilkie, Wendell L., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Woll, Matthew, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Workers Alliance of America, 1937-1940 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Workmen's Compensation: Problems in the Transit Industry, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Works Progress Administration (WPA), 1937-1940 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - World's Fair, New York, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Xavier Labor College: Critique of TWU, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Xavier Labor College: Opening, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Subseries I:B: New York City Council and Other Political Files, 1935-1955.
    - Action to Oust Quill from the New York City Council, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Addison, Chester: Campaign, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Addresses, Broadcast Transcriptions, Articles (Others), 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Addresses, Broadcast Transcriptions, Articles (Quill), 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Addresses, Broadcast Transcriptions, Articles (Quill), 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Addresses, Broadcast Transcriptions, Articles (Quill), Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Amalgamated Utility Workers v. IBEW, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - American Committee for the Protection of the Foreign Born, 1943; 1946 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - American Communications Association: Flyer, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - American Labor Party, 1935; 1937 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - American Labor Party, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - American Labor Party, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - American Labor Party, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - American Labor Party, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - American Labor Party, 1943-1949 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - American Labor Party: Administrative Committee Minutes, 1937-1938 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - American Labor Party: Bronx County, Undated; 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - American Labor Party: Progressive Committee to Rebuild, 1939-1940 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - American Labor Party: Proportional Representation, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - American Labor Party: Sheamus O'Sheel Dispute and Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - American Labor Party: Sound Track Schedules, 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - American Labor Party: Transport Workers Union Break with, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - American League for Tolerance, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - American Peace Mobilization, Astoria Peace Council: Rally, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - American Russian Institute, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - American Youth Congress, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - American Youth Congress: Joint Peace Conference, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Anti-Nazi Rally: Montefiore Congregation, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Anti-War Rallies, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Anti-War Speech (Quill), 1939 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Association of Employees of Incinerators: Mass Meeting, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Association of Harlem and Bronx Property Owners, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Association of Hospital and Medical Employees: Quill Radio Talk, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Austro-American Citizens Committee, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Bill #13, Int. 13: Fire Department Overtime Pay, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Bill #14, Int. 14: Temporary Patrolmen, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Bill #15, Int. 15: Hours and Compensation of Civil Employees, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Bill #16, Int. 16: Uniforms, City Employees, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Bill #30, Int. 30: Temporary Firemen, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Bill #48, (Resolution 91): Cross-Bronx Expressway, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Bill #61, Hours and Compensation of Civil Employees, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Bill #95, Int. 89: Enforcement of Price and Rent Controls ("OPA Bill"), 1944 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Bill #95, Int. 89, Enforcement of Price and Rent Controls ("OPA Bill"), 1945 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Bill #277, Int. 277: Fire Hazards, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Bill #291, Int. 291: Veterans in Public Housing, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Bill #381, Int. 322: Used Car Dealers, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Bill #446, Int. 375: Rodeph Sholom Cemetery, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Bill #450, Int. 450: Building Code (Masonry), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Bill #454, Int. 454: Censorship, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Bill #538, Int. 449: Grade and Pay of Patrolmen, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Bill #672, Int. 562: Taxi Rate Increase, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Bill #1899: Transit Authority Bill, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Bill (H.R. 2232): Discrimination in Employment, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Bill (H.R. 2848): Anti-Semitism (Buckley Bill), 1947 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Bills/Resolutions Introduced by Quill (List), 1944 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Bills and Resolutions: Letters of Support, 1945-1948 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Bills and Resolutions: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Bills and Resolutions: Miscellaneous, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Bills and Resolutions: Miscellaneous, 1946-1949 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Bronx Community Council for Racial and Religious Tolerance: Rally, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity (1), 1944 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity (II), 1944 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity (III), 1943 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity: Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity: Executive Council, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity: Finances, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity: Press Releases, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Bronx County Medical Society: Progressive Bloc, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Bronx Coordinating Committee for Childcare Centers: Finances, 1944-1948 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Bronx Emergency Conference to Save Rent Control, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Bronx Emergency Conference to Save the O.P.A., 1944-1945 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Bronx Emergency Conference to Save the O.P.A (Publicity), 1945 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Bronx, General, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Bronx Local Boards, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Bronx Times, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Battery: Bridge vs. Tunnel, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Citizens League, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Conferences on Legislation, 1945, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Buckley, Charles A.: Campaign, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Cacchione, Peter: Campaign, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Calendar: General Orders and Committee Reports (NY City Council), 1939 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Calendar: New York City Council, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Fund-Raising (I), 1943 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Campaign Fund-Raising (II), 1943 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Campaign Fund-Raising (III), 1943 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Child Care: Quill-O'Keefe Conflict, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Cigarette Stamp Tax, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Citizens and Labor Committee to Uphold Free Elections, Undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Citizens Union of the City of New York, 1939; 1943; 1945 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Coalition: New York City Council (American Labor Party Group), 1938 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cohen, Costuma, et al. (Board of Elections): Petition, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Committee for Defense of Public Education (AFT, Locals 5 and 537), [1943?] (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Committee for People's Rights (Philadelphia): Quill Speech, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Commodore Barry Parkway Committee, Undated (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Conference on Civil, Labor and Minority Rights, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Conference on Victory Legislation, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Conference on Housing and Jobs, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Conference on Unemployment, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Conference on Unfinished Business in Service Legislation, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Conferences, Political Action: I. Blumberg Materials, 1943-1945 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Congress of American-Soviet Friendship, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO): Conferences, 1942-1946 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - CIO Councils: Various States, 1941-1946 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - CIO Endorsed Candidates, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - CIO: General, 1937 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - CIO: General, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - CIO: General, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - CIO: General, 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - CIO: General, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - CIO: General, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - CIO: General, 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - CIO: General, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - CIO: General, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - CIO: General, 1950-1955 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - CIO: Legislative, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - CIO: Legislative (New York), 1938-1948 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - CIO: Resolutions, 1948-1950 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - CIO: "Save the Wagner Act" Pamphlet, Undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - CIO: War Chest, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Connolly, Eugene P.: Campaign, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Constituent Advisement, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Constituent Advisement, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Constituent Advisement (I), 1945 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Constituent Advisement (II), 1945 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Constituent Advisement (I), 1946 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Constituent Advisement (II), 1946 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Constituent Advisement, 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Constituent Advisement (Mostly Landlord-Tenant Issues), 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Constituent Advisement (Mostly Landlord-Tenant Issues), 1945 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Advisement (Mostly Landlord-Tenant Issues), 1946 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Advisement (Mostly Landlord-Tenant Issues), 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Advisement (Mostly Landlord-Tenant Issues), 1947 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Advisement (Mostly Landlord-Tenant Issues), 1948; Undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Constituents: Correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Constituents: Special Cases, 1943-1946; Undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Constituents: Special Cases, 1947-1949 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Constituents: Special Cases, D, 1944-1948 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Constituents: Special Cases, E, 1938-1948; Undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Consumer Issues, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1938 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1938 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Apr 1939 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, May-Aug 1939 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Mar-May 1944 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1944 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jun-Sep 1944 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1944 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Feb 1945 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1945 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1945 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, May 1945 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jun-Jun 1945 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Aug-Oct 1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1945 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1946 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Apr-Jul 1946 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Aug-Dec 1946 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1947 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jan-May 1948 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jun-Dec 1948 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Hate Mail, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Coughlin, Father Charles E., Undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Council of Women Shoppers, Undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Council on African Affairs: Conference, with Paul Robeson and Max Yergan, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Counterattack, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Davis, Benjamin: Campaign, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Democratic Party Meeting: Report, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Dermody, Joseph: Campaign, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Department Store Organizing Committee, Macy's Chapter, 1939; Undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Devaney, John A. v. Quill, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Economists' National Committee on Monetary Policy (Anti-New Deal), 1941 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Education, Undated; 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Election Campaign, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Election Campaign: Committee of 1000 to Elect Quill (TWU), 1937 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Election Campaign: Labor Support for Quill, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Election Campaign: Publicity, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Election Campaign (I), 1939 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Election Campaign (II), 1939 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Election Campaign: Clippings, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Election Campaign: Committee of 1000 to Re-elect Quill, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Election Campaign: Labor Support for Quill, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Election Campaign: Publicity, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Election Campaign: Quill Defeat, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Election Campaign: Speeches, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Election Campaign: Quill Speeches, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Election Campaign, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Election Campaign: Citizens Committee for the Election of Michael J. Quill (I), 1943 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Election Campaign: Citizens Committee for the Election of Michael J. Quill (II), 1943 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Election Campaign: Committee of 1000 to Elect Quill (TWU), 1943 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Election Campaign: Endorsements of Quill, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Election Campaign: Irish-American Support for Quill, [1943] (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Election Campaign: Labor Support for Quill, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Election Campaign: Liberal Party, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Election Campaign: Primary, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Election Campaign: Publicity, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Election Campaign: Quill Speeches, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Election Campaign: Victory Speech to Irish Americans, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Election Campaign, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Election Campaign: American Labor Party, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Election Campaign: Victory Congratulations, Thank-You Letters, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Election Campaign: Publicity, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Election Campaign: Quill Speeches, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Election Campaign, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Election Campaign: American Labor Party, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Election Campaign: Bronx Independent Veterans' Committee, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Election Campaign: Clippings, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Election Campaign: Endorsements, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Election Campaign: Irish-American Support for Quill, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Election Campaign: Labor Support for Quill, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Election Campaign: Liberal Party, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Election Campaign: Nomination of Quill, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Election Campaign: Other Candidates, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Election Campaign: Publicity, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Election Campaign: Quill Platform, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Election Campaign: Quill Speeches, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Election Campaign: Yiddish Flyer and Postcard, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Election Campaign, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Election Campaign: Quill Victory, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Election Campaign (Special Congressional), 1946 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Election Campaign, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Election Campaign: Labor Support for Quill, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Election Campaign: Publicity, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians (FAECT), 1938-1940 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Finances, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Finances, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Finances, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Finances, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Finances, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Finances, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Finances, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade: US Prisoners in Spain, Undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - German-American Committee for Progressive City Administration: Election Rally, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Goldstein, Jonah J: Campaign, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Greater Bronx Civil League, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Greater New York CIO Council, 1944-1946 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Greater New York CIO Council, 1947-1948 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Greater New York CIO Council: CIO Victory News, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Greater New York CIO Council: New York CIO Action Guide, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 34)